(Penny:)- Hold.
RAJESH: Who made Sheldon the boss?
(Sheldon:)I believe I'm hearing some negativity
on the factory floor.
- So?
- The labor force is a living organism...
...that must be nurtured.
(Sheldon:)Any counterproductive grumbling
must be skillfully headed off...
(Sheldon:)...by management. Observe. Hey!
(Sheldon:)Less talk, more work.
- Nicely done.
- Thank you.
(Sheldon:)You hear any union talk,
you let me know.
[SINGING WHILE YAWNING]
Someone's in the kitchen with Dinah
[WHISPERING]
[SINGING]
Someone's in the kitchen I know
Ho, ho, ho
[SINGING]
Someone's in the kitchen with Dinah
Sheldon. Sheldon.
[SINGING]
'Cause I sold my soul
(Sheldon(waking up, singing):)To the company store
- Honey, do you want some coffee?
- No, I don't drink coffee.